我们那时候正坐在商店里有个人进来
We were in a store and a guy in that store...
就叫我们去参军
...told us to put our uniforms on.
"你到底在说什么? "
"what the hell are you talking about? "
他说: "美国与日本开战了"
He says, "The USA is in a war with Japan."
我们压根儿就不敢相信
We couldn't believe it.
我们的国家被攻击了
Well, our country was attacked.
这是不同的
It's different.
这与朝鲜战争或越南战争不同
It wasn't like Korea or Vietnam.
我们被攻击了
We were attacked.
你知道 这种感觉...
And, you know, it was a feeling that...
或许我们是乡下老实人
...maybe, we're just dumb country people but...
但我们很多人都自愿参军
...where I come from a lot of us volunteered.
"谁要自愿加入坦克部队? "
"Who would like to volunteer for the Tank Corps?
"谁要自愿加入空军? "
"Who would like to volunteer for the Air Force?
"谁要自愿加入海军? "
"Who would like to volunteer for the Navy? " or whatever.
他们又说
And then, they said:
"谁愿意加入空降师? "
"Who would like to volunteer for the Airborne? "
什么是"空降"啊?
Somebody says, "What the hell's the Airborne? "
根本没有人听过
Nobody ever heard of it.
我们来自一个很小的城镇
We came from a small, small town.
镇上有三个人因为体检不合格而自杀
And three fellows in that town that were 4F...
因为他们不能从军
...committed suicide because they couldn't go.
真是个不同的年代
A different time.
我们做了些事
I did things.
我们做那些事不是为了勋章
I didn't do them for medals.
我们做那些事不是为了荣誉 我们做那些事只因那是必须做的事
I didn't do them for accolades. I did 'em because it's what had to be done.
有人说: "各位 当你跳出飞机...
The guy says, "would you jump out of airplanes?
"你带着所有陆军给你的配备...
"You know, you got all your army equipment...
"跳出飞机 准备与敌人作战..."
"...and you jump out of airplanes, to fight the enemy."
我们说"去死吧"
These guys, they said, "Go to hell."
没有人举起手
Nobody put up their hands.
我不知道是谁提起的
And then, I don't know what it was brought it up...
但有个人演讲提到
...but the guy giving the speech was saying:
"你一个月可以多赚50块钱"
"But you get paid $50 a month more."
所以那就是100块
So, that made it a hundred bucks.
美国家庭影院 出品
联合制作: 梦工厂 与 PLAYTON公司
领衔主演:科克・阿塞韦多 埃奥恩・贝利 迈克尔・库德利兹
戴尔・德耶 里克・格梅兹 斯科特・格里米斯
弗兰克・约翰・休伊斯 达米安・路易斯 朗・利文斯通
詹姆斯・马迪欧 尼尔・麦克唐纳 雷内・Ｌ・莫雷诺
大卫・休默 理察・斯贝特 唐尼・沃尔伯格
联合执行制片人: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯 加里・高依兹曼 托尼・ 托
执行制片人:汤姆・汉克斯 斯蒂文・斯皮尔伯格
兄弟连作者: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯
编剧:埃里克・延德里森 与 汤姆・汉克斯
导演:菲尔・奥尔登・鲁宾逊
兄 弟 连
第一集
新 兵 训 练
(1944年6月4日)
( 英国 尤波泰瑞 )
...我真想来块鸡肉馅饼
I want a whiff of chicken pie.
弟兄们 把装备都收好
Okay, boys, let's get this gear stowed.
Ｆ连 我们五分钟内出发
Fox Company...we go in five.
以圣父圣子之名
"In the name of the Father..."
第一排准备好轻武器 敌人到了再准备就晚了
1st Platoon, draw small arms.
需要帮忙吗 中尉?
Do you need a hand, Lieutenant?
Ｅ连注意! 整装!
Easy Company! Listen up!
朝我靠拢集合
Gather up around me.
动作快 大家快点
Just move it up. Come on, gentlemen.
快点!
Let's go!
现在英伦海峡笼罩在雨雾之中
Now, the Channel coast is socked in with rain and fog.
空投区风太大
High winds on the drop zone.
今晚不跳了!
No jump tonight.
登陆行动已经延后
The invasion has been postponed.
现在进入24小时戒备状态!
We're on a 24-hour stand-down.
可恶!
Son of a bitch.
各排排长集合部队
Drill sergeants, take charge.
这真是出人意料之外
Well, this is quite a surprise.
倒不见得
Not particularly.
既来之则安之
It so happens I rather expected it.
我实在无法理解你们 怎能为了八万块钱就从军
Well, I can't see how you people can pass up $80,000 for the Cause
我可不是为钱从军的
For whose cause?
如果是为了薪给
If you're so interested in serving a cause...
为何不干脆加入陆军?
...why don't you join the Army?
天气要放晴了
I think it's clearing up.
你觉得会变晴?
You think it's clearing up?
不会
No.
我想是要放晴了
I think it's clearing up.
你的弟兄准备得如何?
How are your men?
他们没问题的
They'll be fine.
现在纽约是五点钟
5:00 in New York.
芝加哥是四点钟
4:00 in Chicago.
快乐时光 对吧?
Happy hour, huh?
是的..
Yeah.
快乐时光
Happy hour.
喝它几杯
A couple of drinks.
或许在看电影前提早吃晚餐
Maybe an early dinner before the theater.
那是文明人享受文明的地方
A civilized place for civilized men.
真该早点出生的 尼克
Should've been born earlier, Nix.
然后抛弃这一切?
What, and give up all this?
我们会去芝加哥的 我带你去
We'll go to Chicago, I'll take you there.
是喔..
Yeah.
再说吧...
We'll see.
事实上 你知道谁是芝加哥人?
Actually, you know who's from there?
谁? 他喔
Who? Oh, him.
忍受他712个日子 我们终于熬过来了
712 days of that son of a bitch and here we are.
( 两年前)
( 塔可亚军营 乔治亚州 )
你们所有人应该立正站好!
You people are at the position of attention.
派康提二等兵 你是学伞兵把裤管塞进靴子里?
Private Perconte, have you been blousing your trousers over your boots like a paratrooper?
没有 长官!
No, sir.
那你的裤脚怎么有皱摺?
Then explain the creases at the bottom.
长官 没有理由
No excuse, sir.
志愿加入空降部队是一回事 派康提
Volunteering for the Parachute Infantry is one thing, Perconte...
但是 要成为伞兵 你还早咧
...but you've got a long way to prove you belong here.
你的周末外出取消了
Your weekend pass is revoked.
名字?
Name?
乔治鲁兹
Luz, George.
准星后方有灰尘
Dirt in the rear side aperture.
外出取消
Pass revoked.
你何时把这些阶级绣上去的 李普中士?
When did you sew on these chevrons, Sergeant Lipton?
昨天 长官
Yesterday, sir.
线头太长 外出取消
Long enough to notice this. Revoked.
是 长官
Sir.
名字?
Name?
唐诺・马拉其!
Malarkey, Donald G.
马拉其?
Malarkey
换成俗语就是狗屎的意思 是吧?
Malarkey's slang for bullshit, isn't it?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
枪托折轴弹簧生锈 二等兵狗屎
Rust on the butt plate hinge spring, Private Bullshit.
外出取消
Revoked.
名字?
Name?
乔瑟夫・李高特 长官
Liebgott, Joseph D., sir.
刺刀生锈 李高特
Rusty bayonet, Liebgott.
你想杀德国佬吗?
You want to kill Germans?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
不是靠这玩意儿
Not with this.
我不会带这块废铁上战场
I wouldn't take this rusty piece of shit to war.
你们这种表现 我也不会带你们上战场
And I will not take you to war in your condition.
由于你们这些人犯错
Now, thanks to these men and their infractions...
连上所有周末外出的人
...every man in the company who had a weekend pass...
全部取消休假
...has lost it.
换上你们的操练服 我们要去跑步
Change into your PT gear, we're running Currahee.
第二排解散
2nd Platoon, fall out.
你们有两分钟时间
We have two minutes.
解散!
Fall out!
我可不想上那座山
I ain't going up that hill.
派康提 你干嘛摺你的裤管?
Perconte, what are you thinking of blousing your pants?
马丁 你闭嘴好吗?
Shut up, okay?
他挑每个人的毛病
He gigged everyone.
那你就应该更小心
You should know better.
不要给他任何借口
Don't give him no excuses.
借口?
Excuses?
你过来看看我的裤子
Why don't you come here, look at these trousers...
蹲下来仔细瞧 告诉我哪里有摺痕?
...get down and tell me if there's a crease?
好了 我们出发了 成体能训练队形
Let's go on the road in PT formation.
动作快!
Let's move, move, move!
派康提 出发了
Perconte, let's go, Perconte.
二等兵怀特 你为什么未着操练服?
Private White, why are you not in your PT gear?
我在问你问题 二等兵
I asked you a question, Private.
Ｅ连的弟兄们
Oh, Easy Company.
专心跑步别担心
While you're running, don't worry.
我们会帮你们带小妞去看电影
We'll take your dames to the movies.
很好 他们需要些女伴
Yeah, good, they need some female company.
我们在哪儿跑步?
Where do we run?
葛拉锡 (新兵营)
Currahee.
那是什么意思?
What does "Currahee" mean?
我们团结一致
We stand alone.
去跑多远? 回跑多远?
How far up, how far down?
前去三里 回来三里
Three miles up, three miles down.
我们叫做什么连?
And what company is this?
Ｅ连
Easy Company.
- 我们该做什么? - 团结一致!
- And what do we do? - Stand alone.
不准帮那个人!
Do not help that man! Do not help that man!
我们不停下
We do not stop.
你们要想在空降部队混
You've got 30 minutes to get to the top of this mountain...
就给我在30分钟内跑上山头
...if you want to serve in the Paratroopers.
冲啊 骏马!
Hi-ho, Silver!
加油 你们跑得到的
You can make it up there.
加油
Come on.
艾利 快跟上
Come on, Alley, let's go.
加油 葛奈瑞
Come on, Guarnere.
克里斯登生 加油
Christenson, come on.
我没想到你办的到 二等兵怀恩
I never thought I'd see the day, Private Wynn.
我们23分钟就跑到了
We are coming on 23 minutes.
这或许对其他506团的部队来说够好了
That may be good enough for the rest of the 506...
但是对Ｅ连而言还不够
...but that is not good enough for Easy Company.
第二排 我们办得到的
We can make it, we can do this, come on.
我有话要说
I'm going to say something.
跟谁说?
To who?
温特斯少尉
Lieutenant Winters.
什么事?
What is it?
请求发言 长官
Permission to speak, sir?
请求许可
Permission granted.
长官 我们一共有9个连
Sir, we got nine companies, sir.
没错
That we do.
为何我们是唯一每周五晚上
How come we're the only company...
都要全副武装摸黑跑12里的一连?
...marching every Friday night, 12 miles, full pack in the pitch dark?
那你以为是为什么呢? 二等兵蓝道曼?
Why do you think, Private Randleman?
索柏中尉恨我们
Lieutenant Sobel hates us, sir.
索柏中尉并不恨Ｅ连 二等兵蓝道曼
Lieutenant Sobel does not hate Easy Company, Private Randleman.
他只恨你一个人
He just hates you.
谢谢你 长官
Thank you, sir.
他也恨他
He hates him back.
他也恨你呢 穆克
He hates you, too, Muck.
温特斯少尉 所有水壶都卸下腰带 盖子打开
Lieutenant Winters, I want canteens out of belts with the caps unscrewed.
全Ｅ连都要卸水壶 把盖子打开
Easy Company, canteens out and open.
听我命令 所有人把水壶里的水倒在地上
On my command, they will pour the contents onto the ground.
听指挥官口令 把水壶倒过来
On the CO's order, you will upend your canteen.
就是现在 少尉
Now, Lieutenant.
倒
Pour them.
这是谁?
Who is this?
克里斯登生
Christenson.
你水壶里为何没水?
Why is there no water in your canteen?
你喝了水 是吧?
You drank from your canteen, didn't you?
温特斯少尉!
Lieutenant Winters.
长官!
Yes, sir.
是不是有规定 不准在周五夜跑喝水?
Was this man ordered to not drink from his canteen during the Friday night march?
是的 长官!
He was, sir.
二等兵克里斯登生 你违反命令
Private Christenson, you have disobeyed a direct order.
把水壶给我装满
You will fill your canteen...
再去跑上12里
...and repeat all 12 miles of the march immediately.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
离开!
Fall out!
你是怎么带我的连?
What in the name of God are you doing with my company?
你不但迟到 还允许士兵违反命令
You're late and you allow troopers to disobey direct orders?
没有理由 长官
No excuse, sir.
你让我很难看 少尉!
You're making me look bad, Lieutenant.
我们不是Ｄ连也不是Ｆ连
This is not Dog Company. This is not Fox Company.
这是Ｅ连
This is Easy Company.
在我领导之下 我们将是第一
Under my command, this will be the first...
也是军团里最好的连
...and finest company in this regiment.
我要你找出六个人
I want the names of six men.
把他们的名字 犯的错误 以及你的教化建言 在1点30分前放在我桌上
Their infractions and your disciplinary recommendations on my desk by 0130.
听清楚了吗?
Is that clear?
什么样的错误 长官?
What infractions, sir?
你去找出来
Find some.
结果你怎么做?
So, what'd you do?
我找了六个人去扫军厕
Picked six men and gave them latrine duty.
哪六个倒霉鬼?
The lucky six?
麦唐纳 托依 派康提
McDowell, Toye, Perconte.
李普 穆克及葛奈瑞
Lipton, Muck and Guarnere.
为何找他们?
Why them?
本来就轮到他们扫
It was their turn.
索柏真是个天才
Sobel's a genius.
我在预校就有个教官像他
I had a headmaster just like him in prep school.
他这种人我很了解
I know the type.
路易斯
Lewis.
米开朗基罗才是天才 贝多芬也是天才
Michelangelo's a genius, Beethoven's a genius.
你知道本连有谁不愿意全付武装跑酷拉练
You know a man in this company who wouldn't double-time Currahee with a full pack...
然后在那个砘锏脑绮涂Х壤锶瞿?
...just to piss in that guy's morning coffee?
赶快 赶快
Let's go, let's go.
- 站到门边 - 跳
Stand in the door.
一秒 两秒
1,000, 2,000.
二等兵戈登 你刚跌断你的双腿
You just broke both your legs, Private Gordon.
你想要自杀吗?
Are you trying to get killed?
不想 长官
No, sir.
站到门边
Stand in the door.
可恶
Shit.
跑到墙边
To the wall.
大家一起过去
Over as a team.
去 靠着墙边
Go on, against the wall.
老天 这是什么玩意儿?
Jesus, what the hell is this?
那是猪
That's pig guts, boy.
可恶!
Goddamn it!
二等兵戈登 你为何来这里?
Why are you here, Private Gordon?
我想成为伞兵 长官
To be in the Airborne, sir.
我不相信 二等兵戈登 你为何来这里?
I don't believe you. Why are you here, Private Gordon?
我想要成为伞兵 长官
To be in the Airborne, sir.
给你50分钟跑到山头再回来 我会盯着你
You have 50 minutes to the top and back, and I will be watching you.
你还在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
Ｅ连在第二营表现最好
Easy Company has the finest performance record in the entire 2nd Battalion.
我相信这全都归功于你
I believe every bit of that is thanks to you.
恭喜你 索柏上尉
Congratulations, Captain Sobel.
谢谢你 长官
Thank you, sir.
正在带穿操练服的Ｅ连操练的 是不是温斯特少尉?
Isn't that Lieutenant Winters leading Easy Company in PT?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
他真是好军人
He's a damned good man.
我今天本要颁发他一副这个
I was planning on giving him a set of these today.
由你来好了 他一定会觉得很荣幸
Why don't you do it? He'd be proud to get them from you.
色情书刊 违禁品
Pornography, contraband.
规定外的衣服 违禁品
Non-regulation clothing, contraband.
这人柜子里有200个保险套
This man had 200 prophylactic kits in his footlocker.
他哪里还有力气打仗?
How in the name of God was he going to have the strength to fight the war?
二等兵提波那里来那么多
How is it Private Tipper...
空闲时间看那么多的信?
...has spare time for so much correspondence?
连长! 私人信件也算违禁品?
Captain, are personal letters to be considered contraband?
这些人还不是伞兵 少尉
These men aren't paratroopers yet, Lieutenant.
他们没有私人物品
They have no personal property.
这是什么?
What is this?
谁愿意回答?
Anybody?
那是罐桃子 长官
It's a can of peaches, sir.
尼克森少尉认为这是罐桃子
Lieutenant Nixon thinks this is a can of peaches.
这是不正确的 少尉
That is incorrect, Lieutenant.
你的周末外出取消了
Your weekend pass is cancelled.
这是美国陆军财产
This is United States Army property...
是从我们伙房未经允许带出的
...which was taken, without authorization, from my mess facility...
而我绝不容忍连上有任何偷窃物品
...and I will not tolerate thievery in my unit.
这是谁的置物柜?
Whose footlocker is this?
二等兵帕克斯的 长官
Private Parks, sir.
把他退训
Get rid of him.
所有周末外出许可取消
All weekend passes are cancelled.
包括军官的
Officers included.
继续动作
Carry on.
温特斯少尉
Lieutenant Winters.
辛克上校觉得你可以晋升了
Colonel Sink has seen fit to promote you.
身为中尉 你将担任我的值星官
As First Lieutenant, you'll serve as my executive officer.
恭喜
Congratulations.
谢谢你 长官
Thank you, sir.
还有 为了训练你的组织能力和领导潜力
And, as a test of your organizational skills and command potential...
我现在指派你担任14天的伙房官
...I am designating you mess officer for 14 days.
5点15到厨房报道
Report to the mess kitchen at 0515 hours.
连上早餐6点开饭
Company breakfast to be served at 0600.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
还有 迪克 气象报告说明天会下雨
And, Dick, there's rain forecast tomorrow...
所以明天下午连上在室内上些轻松的课
...so the company will have a light afternoon of lecture and classroom instruction.
我想在下午休息前来个特别点心
I think a special meal before their afternoon off...
那会是改变步调的好开始
...would be a welcome change of pace.
你同意吗?
Would you agree?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我喜欢意大利面
I like spaghetti.
等等 马上再来
Hold on, more coming.
这些家伙还想打包呢
These guys are packing it away.
这玩意儿是桔色的
This stuff is orange.
意大利面不应该是桔色的
Spaghetti ain't supposed to be orange.
这不是意大利面
This ain't spaghetti.
这是沾了番茄酱的陆军面条
This is army noodles with ketchup.
又没规定你一定得吃
You ain't got to eat it.
拜托 淋病先生 身为意大利人
Oh, come on, Gonorrhea, as a fellow Italian...
称这垃圾为意大利面会良心不安的
...you know that calling this spaghetti is a mortal sin.
- 你不要我要 - 不 我在吃
- I'll have it. - No, I'm eating here.
闪一边去
Hey, get out of here.
命令更改 起立!
Orders changed, get up!
室内课程取消
Lectures are cancelled.
Ｅ连现在改在营区跑步
Easy Company is running up Currahee.
动作快!
Move, move!
去三里 回三里
Three miles up, three miles down.
冲啊 骏马!
Hi-ho, Silver!
出发了
Let's go, let's go.
你是个懦夫 二等兵胡伯勒
You're a washout, Private Hoobler!
你应该把耳朵都打包好回家
You should pack up both your ears and go home.
看来戈登已经不行了
Looks like Gordon's done.
是不是啊 戈登? 你玩完了吗?
Aren't you, Gordon. You finished?
你不配得到你的伞兵勋章
You do not deserve to get your wings.
一等兵蓝道曼 你看来很疲倦
Private Randleman, you look tired.
山脚有辆救护车在等着你
There's an ambulance waiting for you at the bottom of the hill.
你现在就可以解脱
It can all be over right now.
再也没有痛苦 再也没有新兵训练
No more pain, no more Currahee.
再也没有索柏上尉
No more Captain Sobel.
∮我们拉着扬升缆 降落在草地∮
"We pull upon the risers We fall upon the grass
∮我们不用脚落地 永远臀落地∮
"We never land upon our feet We always hit our ass
∮万能之神 我们是何人? ∮
"Hide tidee, Christ almighty Who the hell are we?
∮我们是天杀的伞兵∮
"Zim zam, goddamn! We're Airborne Infantry
∮我们拉着扬升缆 降落在草地∮
"We pull upon the risers We fall upon the grass
∮我们不用脚落地 永远臀落地∮
"We never land upon our feet We always hit our ass
∮万能之神 我们是何人? ∮
"Hide tidee, Christ almighty Who the hell are we?
∮我们是天杀的伞兵∮
"Zim zam, goddamn! We're Airborne Infantry"
你们觉得准备好成为陆军伞兵了吗?
So, do we feel like we're ready to be army paratroopers?
是的 中士
Yes, Sergeant.
我也希望如此
I hope so.
这是我们今天预定从C47上跳五次的第一趟
This'll be the first of five exits from a C-47 aircraft scheduled for today.
准备
Get ready!
起立
Stand up!
挂钩
Hook up!
一旦你跳完五次 也是最后一跳
Upon successful completion of your fifth and final jump...
你就成为合格的伞兵
...you'll be certified army paratroopers.
检查装备!
Check equipment!
报告检查装备
Sound off for equipment check!
9号就绪
Nine okay.
8号就绪
Eight okay.
7号就绪
Seven okay.
6号就绪
Six okay.
5号就绪
Five okay.
4号就绪
Four okay.
3号就绪
Three okay.
2号就绪
Two okay.
1号就绪
One okay.
今天会有许多人从天而降
There'll be a lot of men dropping from the sky today.
希望大家的伞都能开
Hopefully, under deployed canopies.
站到门口
Stand in the door!
我保证你会喜欢的 中尉
I guarantee you're going to love it, Lieutenant.
跳!
Go, go!
我们从实际高度一千尺跳
Jumping from 1,000 feet AGL...
一架飞机一梯次跳12个人
...in sticks of 12 jumpers per aircraft.
你们只要牢记所学的
All you have to do is remember what you were taught...
我保证剩下的就让地心引力去完成了
...and I guarantee you, gravity will take care of the rest.
跳!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
跳!
可恶
Damn it.
各位 还有最重要的...
And, gentlemen, rest assured...
任何在机舱里或是门边拒跳的人
...any refusals in the aircraft or at the door...
我保证你会被踢出空降部队
...and I guarantee you, you will be out of the Airborne.
4号就绪
Four okay.
3号就绪
Three okay.
2号就绪
Two okay.
1号就绪
One okay.
站到门口
Stand in the door.
跳!
Go!
一秒 两秒 三秒 四秒 五秒 六秒
1,000, 2,000, 3,000, 4,000, 5,000, 6,000...
七秒 八秒 九秒!
...7,000, 8,000, 9,000!
冲啊 骏马
Hi-ho, Silver!
你想想 如果你像我一样帅
Now just think, if you had any class or style like me...
别人可能以为你是个大人物
...somebody might mistake you for somebody.
你是说像个班长?
You mean like your fucking sergeant?
开玩笑而已
I'm just kidding.
恭喜你 马丁
Congratulations, Martin.
托依下士! 在我连里是不容许任何偏差的
Corporal Toye, there will be no leaning in my company.
这是沾了灰尘的伞兵徽吗?
Are those dusty jump wings?
伞兵徽要是沾上灰 怎能用来杀德国佬呢?
How do you expect to slay the Huns with dust on your jump wings?
鲁兹 给我杯酒就是了
Luz, just give me a drink.
当然
Hell of an idea, Joe.
拿去
There you go.
去三里 回三里
Three miles up, three miles down.
立正!
Ten-hut!
伞兵们 请稍息
Well, at ease, paratroopers.
Ｅ连的弟兄大家晚安
Good evening, Easy Company.
晚安 长官
Evening, sir.
伞兵部队在美国军队史上
Now, Parachute Infantry is a brand-new concept...
是个崭新的概念
...in American military history.
但506团绝对有能力将这新观念
But, by God, the 506 is going to forge that brand-new concept...
转化为胜利
...into victory.
是的 长官!
Yes, sir.
我要你们知道我是多么的以你们为荣
I want you to know that I'm damned proud of each and every one of you.
这场宴会是你们应得的
Now, you deserve this party.
谢谢你 葛兰特中士
Thank you, Sergeant Grant.
长官
Sir.
现在我要你们尽情享受 并牢记我们的座右铭:
So, I want you to have fun and remember our motto:
团结一致!
Currahee!
( 1943年6月23日 )
( 北卡罗莱纳州 麦考军营 )
派提!
Petty.
拿地图来
Map.
快点!
Come on.
老天
Ah, Christ.
我们的位置不对
We're in the wrong position.
长官 我们处于教范中伏击的位置
We're textbook position for ambush, sir.
我们应该静候 让敌人进入我们的猎杀范围
We should sit tight, let the enemy team come into our killing zone.
他们就在附近
They're right out there somewhere.
我们去消灭他们吧
Let's just get them.
长官 这里有绝佳的屏障
Sir, we have perfect cover here.
中尉 部署你的弟兄
Lieutenant, deploy your troops.
第二排! 前进!
2nd Platoon, move out.
什么?
What?
成战术纵队
Tactical column.
连长 你刚跟连上95%的士兵都阵亡了
Captain, you've just been killed, along with 95 percent of your company.
你们的番号?
Your outfit?
506团 第二营 Ｅ连
Easy Company, 2nd Battalion, 506th.
留下三个受伤士兵 然后向集结区报道
Leave three wounded men on the ground and report back to the assembly area.
可恶..
Goddamn it.
你 你 你
You, you, you.
你要怎么办?
Well, what are you going to do?
不怎么办 继续训练他们
Nothing, just keep training the men.
我打搅你们了?
Am I interrupting?
没有
No, no.
路易斯尼克森中尉
Lieutenant Lewis Nixon.
这是刚从82师调来的哈利威尔旭中尉
Lieutenant Harry Welsh, just in from the 82nd.
恭喜你荣升了
Congratulations on the promotion.
谢谢 如果那算是晋升
Thanks, if you want to call it that.
你很快就会发现他是个
You'll learn him pretty quickly.
没缺点 没怪癖 没有幽默感的人
No flaws, no vices, no sense of humor.
就像你在营部的朋友一样
Just like your chums up at battalion staff.
什么事?
What's up?
我听到许多是非
I'm hearing a lot of rumblings.
关于索柏?
Sobel?
我们正在谈这事
Just talking about that.
他在野战场上有些神经质?
So, he gets a little jumpy in the field?
对 他一神经你就阵亡
He gets jumpy and then you get killed.
那真好
That's nice.
是啊 听好了 如果要讨论 仅限于内部
Yeah, listen, if we discuss it, I think it should just be amongst ourselves.
那当然
Absolutely.
第二排准备好了吗?
2nd Platoon, ready?
准备好了 长官
Ready, sir.
那就叫他们整队
Then get them in formation.
我们要出发了
We're moving out.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
卡伯 闭嘴
Shut up, Cobb.
你应该承认的
You got to admit it.
他没有机会的
He's got no chance.
他若非被德军做掉 就是自己人动手
Either the Krauts will get him or one of us.
说谁? 索柏吗?
Who, Sobel?
他搞砸了一个演习
He screwed up one maneuver.
你知道我常把玩手榴弹
Well, you know, I'm always fumbling with grenades.
要是不小心炸掉一枚是很容易的事
It would be easy if one went off by accident, you know?
他们让他负责指挥一定有原因
Well, now they must have put him in charge for a reason.
因为陆军从不犯错 是吗 西福弟
Yeah, 'cause the Army wouldn't make a mistake, right?
跟我一起走吗?
Going my way?
火车去哪我就去哪
Wherever the train takes me.
那会是哪里?
Where do you suppose that might be?
我不知道
I haven't got a clue
来吧 猜猜看
Yeah, come on, take a guess.
大西洋? 太平洋? 大西洋?
Atlantic, Pacific, Atlantic?
我又不是情报局的军官
I'm not the intelligence officer.
我是知道要去哪 但我告诉你就得杀了你
Well, as such, I, of course, know, but if I told you, I'd have to kill you.
那就别告诉我
So, don't tell me.
先到纽约
New York City.
上兵船
Troopship.
再到英国
England.
我们要登陆欧洲 兄弟
We're invading Europe, my friend.
攻击欧罗巴壁垒
Fortress Europa.
我何时开始喝酒了?
Since when do I drink?
我如果知道你喝酒 才不会请你喝
If I thought you'd drink it, I wouldn't offer it to you.
尼克?
Nix?
你从战场上回来后会干什么?
What are you going to do when you get into combat?
我行骗取巧样样行
I have every confidence in my scrounging abilities.
而且你柜子里还藏有一箱陈年威士忌呢
And I have a case of VAT 69 hidden in your footlocker.
真的吗?
Really?
当然
Oh, yeah.
早安
'Morning.
这将会是趟美好旅程
This could turn into a real nice trip.
( 1943年9月6日)
( 布鲁克林海军船坞 )
亲爱的先生女士
"Dear sir or madam:
你们的儿子很快就要从天而降 跟敌人作战并击败他们
"Soon your son will drop from the sky to engage and defeat the enemy.
你们爱与鼓励的信
"Your frequent letters of love and encouragement...
将可武装他战斗的心
"...will arm him with a fighting heart.
借着它 他不会失败而会为自己赢得荣耀
"With that he cannot fail, but will win glory for himself...
让你们以他为荣 而国家也感谢他
"...make you proud of him, and his country ever grateful...
在国家需要的时候 挺身而出
"...for his service in its hour of need.
署名: 贺博索柏 上尉连长
"Signed, Herbert M. Sobel, Captain Commanding."
( 萨玛里亚号 救生衣 )
就在此刻 已经有许多走狗屎运的人 朝着南太平洋出发
Right now, some lucky bastard's headed for the South Pacific.
好想跟他们换
Oh, what I'd give.
被分配到某热带小岛
He's going to get billeted on some tropical island.
继续说
Keep talking.
跟当地的六个裸体的女孩坐在棕榈树下
Sitting under a palm tree with six naked native girls...
她们帮他剥椰子 所以他可以用手来喂火烈鸟
...helping him cut up coconuts so he can hand-feed them to the flamingos.
火烈鸟很凶
Flamingos are mean.
会咬人的
They bite.
裸女也会的
So do the naked native girls.
如果运气好
With any luck.
大伙们 我很高兴要去欧洲
Hey, guys, I'm glad I'm going to Europe.
我在希特勒喉管上割一刀
Hitler gets one of these right across the windpipe.
罗斯福会把感恩节改成乔托依纪念日
Roosevelt changes Thanksgiving to Joe Toye Day...
还要终生每年付我一万元
...and pays me $10,000 a year for the rest of my fucking life.
如果我们不是去欧洲呢?
What if we don't get to Europe?
如果他们送我们去北非呢?
What if they send us to North Africa?
我老哥就在北非
My brother's in North Africa.
他说那里很热
He says it's hot.
真的? 非洲很热?
Really, it's hot in Africa?
闭嘴!
Shut up.
重点是无论我们去哪里
The point is, it don't matter where we go.
一旦我们进入战斗 你唯一可信任的
In combat, the only person you can trust...
就是你自己和身旁的人
...is yourself and the fellow next to you.
只要他是个伞兵
Hey, as long as he's a paratrooper.
是吗?
Oh, yeah?
万一那个伞兵是索柏?
And what if that paratrooper turns out to be Sobel?
若作战时我旁边是索柏 我会移动战线
If I'm next to Sobel in combat, I'm moving on down the line.
去找其他的军官 像是海立格或是温特斯
Hook up with some other officer, like Heyliger or Winters.
我喜欢温特斯 他是个好人
I like Winters, he's a good man.
可是当子弹开始飞舞时
But when the bullets start flying...
我不知道我是不是要让个贵格教徒为我作战
...I don't know if I want a Quaker doing my fighting for me.
你怎么知道他是贵格教徒?
How do you know he's a Quaker?
他绝不是天主教徒
He ain't Catholic.
索柏也不是
Neither is Sobel.
他是个犹太佬
That prick's a son of Abraham.
他是什么?
He's what?
他是犹太人
He's a Jew.
我也是犹太人
I'm a Jew.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
快从我面前消失
Get your nose out of my face.
那是怎么回事?
What's all that about?
淋病先生说索柏是犹太人
Gonorrhea called Sobel a Jew.
李高特跟他冲起来 因为他自己也是犹太人
Liebgott took offense 'cause he's a Jew too.
为了索柏打架 真是聪明
Fighting over Sobel, that's smart.
( 1943年9月18日)
( 英国 爱德布恩 )
攻击!
Attack!
不对 你要有杀气
No, you want to kill him!
防右刺 防左刺
Parry right, parry left.
原地突刺!
Thrust!
还原
Take cover.
好了
Okay.
昨天我们谈到了磁场偏移
Yesterday, we talked about magnetic declination...
以及左加右减定律
...and the "left add, right subtract" rule.
今天我们将实地操作
Today we're putting it into practice.
作战有两种基本位置
There are two basic types of fighting positions.
第一种是守备位置
The first is the prepared position.
守备位置的优点是它提供你掩护及隐蔽
The advantages of a prepared position are that it gives you cover and concealment.
开始射击!
Commence fire!
然后我们都将朝这树林移动
We'll then maneuver right in through these trees.
同时 在这个例子下 第二排将移动到这里
At the same time, our second platoon, in this particular case, moves over here.
他接着将封锁消灭或俘虏德军
He's then going to close with and kill or capture that German.
索柏迟了
Sobel's late.
这里为什么会有围篱?
Why is there a fence here?
这里不应该有围篱
There should be no fence here.
- 提波! - 是的 长官!
- Tibbo - Yes, sir
地图给我
Give me the map.
派康提 鲁兹 集合弟兄
Perconte, Luz.
叫他们...
Get the men, get them...
在树后找掩护
Take cover behind those trees.
都听到了 动作快
You heard the word. Let's go over there.
这里不应该有围篱
There should be no... There should be no fence here.
我们可以跨越它 长官
We could go over it, sir.
真的吗?
Really?
这不是重点 我们到底...
That's not the point. Where the goddamn...
在什么鬼地方?
Where the goddamn hell are we?
- 派康提? - 干嘛?
- Perconte? - Yeah.
- 索柏又迷路了 对不对? - 是啊 他迷路了
- Sobel's lost again, right? - Yeah, he's lost.
真该死
Fucking Christ.
你会模仿贺顿少校吗?
Can you do Major Horton?
- 小子 有人脱裤子放屁的吗? - 安静
Does a wild bear crap in the woods, son?
或许这位好少校能耍耍这笨蛋
Maybe the good major can goose this schmuck.
让我们继续前进吧?
Get us moving?
不 门儿都没有
No way.
要 你一定要
Yes. You got to.
好啦 下不为例
All right, just this once.
三...五...六...八...三...三
Three-five-six-eight-three-three.
这不就是交会点吗?
Isn't that the intersection?
不 长官 是在这里
No, sir, it's here.
你偏离整个坐标格了
You're a full grid off.
可恶
Goddamn it.
索柏上尉 有什么问题吗?
Is there a problem, Captain Sobel?
谁在说话?
Who said that?
是谁违反通话静默?
Who broke silence?
我想那是贺顿少校 长官
I think it's Major Horton, sir.
贺顿少校?
Major Horton?
他怎么...他也参加演习了吗?
What is he... Did he join us?
我想也许他是在各排间游走 长官
I think maybe he's moving between the platoons, sir.
索柏先生 你停止不动 是在搞什么鬼?
What is the goddamn holdup, Mr. Sobel?
有座篱笆 长官
A fence, sir.
我的天
God!
有座铁刺围篱
A barbed wire fence.
那只狗就是不会打猎
Oh, that dog just ain't going to hunt!
你现在把铁网剪了 叫你的排继续前进
Now, you cut that fence and get this goddamn platoon on the move!
是 长官!
Yes, sir!
我那该死的剪线器在哪里?
Where are my goddamn wire cutters?
我们必须前进
We have to move.
长官 不等索柏连长跟第一排了吗?
Sir, without Captain Sobel and 1st Platoon?
这是个"T"字形交汇点 我们自行发挥
It's a T-intersection. We improvise.
以火力掩护双重的包围 封锁道路四方
Double envelopment laid on a base of fire to cut the road in all directions.
向右与第一班会合 叫葛奈瑞和第二班向左移动
Hook right with first squad. Tell Guarnere to move left with second.
我会和第三班从中线突破
I'll be right up the middle with third, go.
是的 长官!
Yes, sir.
我的天
Deary me.
搞什么鬼
Bloody hell.
你成功了 美国佬
You've done it now, Yanks.
你抓到我了
You've captured me.
冲啊~ 骏马!
Hi-ho, Silver!
那是你们的敌人吗?
Would that be the enemy?
事实上 是的
As a matter of fact, yes.
干得好 第二排
Good work, 2nd Platoon.
我们攻占目标了
We took the objective.
哪个白痴把那个人的篱笆给剪了?
Who is the idiot who cut that man's fence?
有人命令我剪的 长官
I was ordered to, sir.
是谁?
By whom?
贺顿少校 长官
Major Horton, sir.
贺顿少校?
Major Horton?
是的 长官!
Yes, sir.
贺顿少校叫你这么做?
Major Horton told you to do that?
是的 长官!
Yes, sir.
贺顿少校命令你把围篱剪了?
Major Horton ordered you to cut the fence?
是的 他说的
Yes, he did.
贺顿少校正在伦敦休假
Major Horton is on leave in London.
把那些牛赶走
Get those cows out of here.
温特斯中尉
Lieutenant Winters.
我带来了索柏上尉的"嘉勉" 长官
With Captain Sobel's compliments, sir.
中尉
Lieutenant.
我的天啊
Oh, for crying out loud.
我看要军法审判了
This spells court-martial.
空位投篮!进了
Wide open! Yes.
不是的 长官 我不明白
No, sir, I do not understand.
你的命令是要我在10点时检查厕所
Your orders to me were to inspect the latrines at 1000 hours.
从9点30到9点55 我奉史崔尔上校的命令查阅士兵们的信件
From 0930 to 0955 I was censoring the enlisted men's mail by order of Colonel Strayer.
10点整 我分秒不差执行了你的命令
At 1000 hours I followed your orders to the minute.
我把时间改到9点45了
I changed that time to 0945.
没人告诉我 长官
No one told me, sir.
我打过电话
I telephoned.
我的排上没有电话
I'm quartered with a family that has no telephone.
我还派了传令兵
And sent a runner.
传令兵没有找到我 上尉
No runner found me, Captain.
不管那么多 当上属长官指派任务时
Irregardless, when given a task to perform by a ranking officer
你应将检查厕所的工作 移交给其他军官
you should have delegated your task of latrine inspection to another officer.
你并未这样做
You failed to do so.
难道要我不处罚犯错的值星官
Were I to let such a failure of duty by my own X O go unpunished...
那样士兵们会怎样想?
...what kind of message is that to the men?
我照命令执行了任务 长官
I performed my duty as I was ordered, sir.
但我不认为
And I disagree.
所以你现在的选择很简单 中尉
So, your options are quite simple, Lieutenant.
对你错误的处罚 将是60天内48小时不许外出
Punishment for your offenses will be denial of a 48-hour pass for 60 days.
在我面前立正站好
Stand before me at attention.
或者你可以上诉 并要求召开军事法庭
Or you may initiate a letter of appeal and request a trial by court-martial.
反正你周末休假都待在营区 迪克
You spend your weekends on the base anyway, Dick.
像个男子汉接受处罚吧
Be a man, take the punishment.
能跟你借个笔吗 长官?
May I borrow your pen, sir?
我的签署 长官
My endorsement, sir.
我要求开军事法庭
I request trial by court-martial.
温特斯被调去营部伙房了
We lost Winters to battalion mess.
你在开玩笑吧?
You're shitting me.
真的!
No.
史崔尔调的 为了让他们能想出军法审判他的程序
Strayer did it, while they try to figure out the procedures for his court-martial.
那尼克最好挖个洞把他救援出来
Nix better find a loophole and get him out.
万一他不出来呢?
And if he don't?
我们和索柏大空降的时候 温特斯却在炒蛋
Winters scrambles eggs while the rest of us make the big jump with Sobel.
别叫我去
Not me.
所以我们决定这么做了?
So we're going through with this, right?
我们总得做点什么
We've got to do something.
好
Yeah.
好吧..
All right.
好吧...
Good.
我们最好都清楚要承担的后果
But we'd all better be clear on the consequences.
- 我才不在乎后果 - 要在乎
- I don't care about the consequences. - You got.
我们可能排排站被枪毙
We could be lined up against a wall and shot.
我已经做好这样的准备
Now, I'm ready to face that.
大家最好也都准备好
And every one of us had better be, too.
我不会跟随那个人作战
I will not follow that man into combat.
我也不会
Me neither.
很好
All right.
我们就这么做
Then let's do it.
我在此声明
"I hereby...
不愿再担任
"...no longer wish to serve...
士官
"...as a non-commissioned officer...
管理Ｅ连
"...in Easy Company."
很好 诸位
All right, boys.
祝好运!
Good luck.
我应把你们都枪毙
I ought to have you all shot!
在我们准备反攻欧洲的时候
This is nothing less than an act of mutiny...
这跟军事叛乱没有两样
...while we prepare for the goddamn invasion of Europe.
哈理士中士
Sergeant Harris.
是的 长官
Sir.
缴交军徽 收拾装备
Turn in your stripes, collect your gear.
我要调你离开我的团
You are hereby transferred out of my regiment.
是的 长官
Sir.
离开
Get out.
蓝尼中士
Sergeant Ranney.
长官
Sir.
算你走运 我只把你降为二等兵
You consider yourself lucky, I'm only busting you to private.
你们这些士官已经让101空降师蒙羞
All of you NCOs have disgraced the 101st Airborne.
因为我们正在历史上最大战役的前夕
Consider yourself lucky that we are on the eve of the largest action in the history of warfare...
我只好饶了你们的性命
...which leaves me no choice but to spare your lives.
离开我的办公室 别让我看到你们
Now, get out of my office and get out of my sight.
离开
Get.
继续搬给我 很好 就是这样
Keep them coming, atta-boy.
我只能这样猜想 长官 大部分人不会这么做
I can only speculate, sir. Most of the men would never do this...
但有少部分的士官
...but I believe just a few of the sergeants may have felt...
觉得对排上的忠诚高于对连上
...their loyalty lay more to the platoon than to the company.
而这些少数军官说服连上其他士官
And these few sergeants convinced all of the other NCOs in your company...
将他们的军阶交出?
...to turn in their stripes?
作为幕僚士官 他们影响力很大 长官
As staff sergeants, they have a great amount of influence, sir.
可是就像我说的 其他的都是好人
But as I say, the rest are good men.
我了解他们 我可以和他们共事
I know them, I can work with them.
关于将温斯特交付军法一事
This business with the Winters' court-martial...
已经造成不愉快的骚动
...has been an unpleasant distraction.
的确 的确是这样的 长官
Indeed it has, sir.
总之
However...
你对Ｅ连的领导一直可为模范
...your command of Easy Company has been exemplary.
谢谢你 长官
Thank you, sir.
事实上 除了这些少数士官的行为外
In fact, except for the actions of a few of your non-coms...
我相信你所统领的是我所见过最好的连队
...I believe you've fielded one of the finest companies of soldiers I've ever seen.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
贺博! 师部
Herbert, Division has established...
已经在奇顿佛列建了一所伞兵训练学校
...a parachute training school at Chilton Foliat.
目的是让在即将展开的登陆中
The idea is for non-infantry types who...
非步兵的重要人员
...were vital to the coming invasion...
如医生及牧师参加跳伞训练
...such as doctors and chaplains, to take jump training there.
坦白说 除你之外我想不出
I can't think of anyone more qualified...
更适合去该校指导的人
...to command such a school than you are.
长官?
Sir?
我将你转调到奇顿佛列
I'm reassigning you to Chilton Foliat.
我要离开Ｅ连?
I'm losing Easy Company?
战争需要你去别的地方
The war effort needs you elsewhere.
请求发言 长官
Permission to speak, sir?
请求许可
Granted.
谁会来替代我?
Is... Who will be replacing me?
Ｂ连的米汉中尉比较资深
Lieutenant Meehan from Baker Company is senior.
祝你在奇顿佛列好运 贺博
Good luck at Chilton Foliat, Herbert.
别让我们失望了
Don't let us down now.
我不会的 长官
No, sir.
继续工作
Carry on.
( 1944年5月31日)
( 英国 尤波泰瑞 )
第二排听好
2nd Platoon, listen up.
我要一班在这边搭帐篷
I want the first squad and A-side tents right up there.
第三班 到第二列
Third squad, second row...
我的老天
Holy shit.
没关系的 老兄 我们是英军
No, it's all right. We're tommies...
不是死德军
...not bleeding boche.
这是真的吗?
Is all this real?
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
有些是从赫曼裁缝店赶工缝制
Some is from the Hermans, somebody's tailor's knocked up.
用来给你们用馅饼砸德国佬的
For you, so you can get your mince pies on this Jerry clobber...
如果你懂我的意思
...if you know what I mean.
不太懂
Not really.
老兄 有鲁格枪(德军手枪)?
Mack, you got a Luger?
我好想摸摸真的鲁格枪
I'm dying to get a real Luger.
有啊 拿去
Yeah, go on then.
真是把好枪 对不?
A quick butchers, yeah?
乖乖 她真是棒极了
Boy, she sure is a doozy.
她真是高级 对不?
Yeah, it's pukka, ain't it?
什么?
What?
派提!
Hey, Petty.
老兄
Hey, mate.
你可别得寸进尺
You're having a bath if you think you're half-inching that.
哦 对
Oh, yeah.
抱歉! 祝你好运!
Sorry. Well, good luck.
你也是 老兄
You too, mate.
什么事 胡伯?
What's up, Hoobs?
这些人经历了陆军最严格的训练
These men have been through the toughest training the Army has to offer.
在极艰困的环境下
Under the worst possible circumstances.
而且这些人都是自愿从军
And they volunteered for it.
拜托 迪克 我不过是跟他们掷骰子 又不是...
Christ, I was just shooting craps with them. It's not like...
你知道他们为什么自愿吗?
You know why they volunteered?
情况变得很糟时 壕沟中身旁的都将是上上之才
So, when things got really bad, the man next to them would be the best.
而不是会害死他们的充数兵
Not some draftee who's going to get him killed.
难道你因为他们喜欢我而不高兴?
Are you ticked because they like me?
因为我花时间去了解我的弟兄?
Because I'm spending time to get to know my soldiers?
拜托 你和他们相处两年了吧?
You've been with these guys for what, two years?
我才来这里六天
I've been here for six days.
你是在赌博 鲍伯
You're gambling, Bob.
那又怎样? 阿兵哥都赌博
So what? Soldiers do that.
这不值得你训我
I don't deserve a reprimand for it.
如果你赢了呢?
What if you'd won?
什么?
What?
如果你赌赢了怎么办?
What if you'd won?
千万不要给自己有任何占士兵便宜的机会
Never put yourself in a position where you can take from these men.
米汉中尉?
Lieutenant Meehan?
进来
Enter.
在上次的跳伞练习 我带着罗盘
On the last training jump, I had a compass.
把帐帘放下
Close the flap.
然后我们向左转
Then we turn left.
对
Yeah.
航线042度
Bearing zero-four-two.
飞12分钟
12 minutes.
然后再左转?
Then another left?
- 对! - 对!
- Yes - Yeah
算是258度吧
Call it three-five-eight...
飞了十分半钟
...for 10 and a half minutes.
绿灯亮起 正在兰姆斯柏瑞上方
Green light, right over Ramsbury.
兰姆斯柏瑞
Ramsbury.
每次都是一样
Every single time.
用你图上的格数计算是从...
Linear distance on the grid of about...
嗯
Okay.
兰姆斯柏瑞
Ramsbury.
尤波泰瑞
Upottery.
所以...
So...
这是诺曼底
It's Normandy.
圣梅莉山岭
St. Marie du Mont.
一号堤道
Causeway Number One.
二号堤道
Causeway Number Two.
最大的战地问题
The ultimate field problem.
多佛河口分成两个滩头
The estuary of the Douve River divides two beachheads...
代号是犹他 这里 还有是奥马哈 这里
...code-named Utah, here, and Omaha, here.
海运步兵大批抵达这些滩头...
Seaborne Infantry will hit these beaches in force...
...有待指定日期与时刻
...at a date and time to be specified.
代号H时 D日
H-hour, D-day.
空降部队的目标是拿下卡汉坦或叫卡云坦
Airborne's objective, gentlemen, is to take the town of Carentan...
借以将犹他及奥马哈连成一线
...thus linking Utah and Omaha into a single, continuous beachhead.
...借以将犹他及奥马哈连成一线
...linking Omaha and Utah into one continuous beachhead.
每位伞兵心里都要将任务牢记在心
Each trooper will learn this operation by heart...
并了解自己其他兵种协同任务的每个细节
...and know his and every other outfits' mission to the detail.
米汉中尉?
Meehan?
什么事 杜克曼?
Yes, Dukeman.
长官 我们今晚跳吗?
Sir, are we dropping tonight?
该让你知道的时候会告诉你
When it's time for you to know, we'll let you know.
与此同时 研究这个沙盘地图以及侦察照片
In the meantime, study these sand tables, maps, and reconnaissance photos...
直到你可以靠记忆画出这一区的地图
...until you can draw a map of the area by memory.
我们将在第四步兵师登陆犹他滩头前的五小时
Now, we will drop behind this Atlantic wall five hours
降落在这个大西洋防线之后
before the 4th Infantry lands at Utah.
在集结区及空降营目标之间
And between our assembly area and the battalion's objective...
这里有个德军的守卫部队 防守着圣梅莉山头
...there is a German garrison right here in this area, St. Marie du Mont.
Ｅ连将负责歼灭该军
Easy Company will destroy that garrison.
三天份的口粮 巧克力棒 精力糖
Three-day supply of K rations, chocolate bars, charms, candy...
咖啡粉 砂糖跟火柴
...powdered coffee, sugar, and matches.
罗盘 刺刀 土工器具 弹药 防毒面具
Compass, bayonet, entrenching tool, ammunition, gas mask.
携物袋加预备弹药 我的伪装网 45手枪 水壶
Musette bag with ammo, my webbing, my.45, canteen...
两包烟
...two cartons of smokes.
霍金式地雷 两枚手榴弹 烟雾弹 伽玛弹
Hawkins mine, two grenades, smoke grenade, gamma grenade...
炸药 这鬼玩意 还有件脏内衣
...TNT, this bullshit, and a pair of nasty skivvies.
你到底什么意思?
What's your point?
这些东西和我的体重相当
This weighs as much as I do.
我还要带降落伞 副伞 救生衣 M1步枪
I've still got my chute, my reserve chute, my Mae West, my M-1.
那你的指节铜套要放哪里?
Where are you keeping your brass knuckles?
我或许会用得上指节铜套的
I could use some brass knuckles.
费斯特 有给我的吗?
Hey, anything for me?
没有
No.
马丁中士
Sergeant Martin.
泰伯特!
For Talbert.
很重呢 保险套吗?
Heavy! condoms?
我不知道 也许是吧
I don't know, probably.
信上写的什么?
What you got?
"亲爱的佛洛依德 让敌人都下地狱"
"Dear Floyd: Give them hell."
是柯科摩警察局长寄来的
It's from the chief of the Kokomo Police.
对
Right.
这些警察真是可爱
You've got to love cops.
好了 注意听
All right, listen up, listen up.
如果你还没签你的大兵人寿险单
If you did not sign your GI life insurance policy...
现在就去总部连办公室找依凡斯中士
...you go on over and see Sergeant Evans at the headquarters company tent.
可别让你们的家人平白损失一万元
You boys don't let your families miss out on $10,000.
你听到了吗 杰瑞?
You hear that, Gerry?
李普?
Hey, Lip?
什么事?
Yeah, boy.
葛奈瑞有告诉你关于他老哥的事吗?
Has Guarnere said anything about his brother?
没有
No.
我们有麻烦了
I got a problem.
我老婆在美国随时注意消息 如阵亡名单
My wife keeps up with things back home, casualty lists and like that.
怎么?
Yeah?
葛奈瑞的老哥在意大利?
Guarnere's brother in Italy?
亨利?
Henry?
在蒙地卡西诺阵亡
Killed in Monte Cassino.
我确定他并不知道
Well, I'm sure he doesn't know.
糟糕
Damn.
你觉得我该怎么做?
What'd you think I should do?
如果是我 我会告诉他
If it were me, I'd tell him.
就在跳伞前几小时?
Couple of hours before we jump?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们干嘛现在把这些东西加挂在我们身上?
Why are they springing these things on us now?
多了80磅的重量绑在你的腿上
It's just an extra 80 pounds strapped to your leg.
有没有知道这鬼玩意儿怎么用?
Does anybody have any idea how the hell this thing works?
辛克上校给你的
Colonel Sink.
团里的各位弟兄:
"Soldiers of the regiment.
今晚就是大战的第一晚
"Tonight is the night of nights.
当你在看这封信时
"Today, as you read this...
你正踏上前往伟大历险的征途上
"...you are en route to the great adventure for which you have trained...
为此你已受训两年多
"...for over two years."
那就是为什么给我们冰淇淋吃
So, that's why they gave us ice cream.
Ｅ连注意!
Easy Company, listen up!
海峡对岸雨雾弥漫
Channel coast is socked in with rain and fog.
今晚不跳了
No jump tonight.
登陆行动已经延后了
The invasion has been postponed.
我们现在进入24小时预备状态
We're on a 24-hour stand-down.
这真是出人意料之外
Well, this is quite a surprise.
倒不见得
Not particularly.
既来之则安之
It so happens I rather expected it.
我实在无法理解你们 怎能为了八万块钱就从军
Well, I can't see how you people can pass up $80,000 for the Cause.
我可不是为钱从军的
For whose cause?
如果是为了薪给的话
If you're so interested in serving a cause...
为什么不干脆加入陆军算了?
...why don't you join the Army?
下一位请
Next, please.
我穿4M
Oh, 4F.
你看来像是穿1A号
You look 1A to me.
你本人比较好看
You don't look so bad yourself.
"亲爱的强尼"
"Dearest Johnny"?
你是不是该捐个血?
Well, should you be giving blood?
我醒来了
I woke up.
我穿到别人的外套
I got the wrong goddamn jacket.
我好象触电一样
I was struck by lightning.
没有人在跳舞
Nobody dancing.
没有关系
It doesn't matter.
"比尔葛奈瑞的哥哥"
"Your pal, Bill Guarnere's brother..."
( 1944年6月5日 )
( 尤波泰瑞机场 )
祝你们好运
Good luck, lads.
再见了 英国大兵
See you, tommies.
帮我修理德国佬
See you, mate.
试穿你的脚束
Try and get these leg straps through.
强尼?
Johnny?
你大概找这个很久了
Got something you might be looking for.
我不小心拿错了
Took your jacket by mistake.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你看了吗?
You read it?
蒙地卡西诺在哪里?
Where the fuck is Monte Cassino?
我不知道 意大利某处吧
I don't know. Italy somewhere.
很遗憾听到你哥的消息 比尔
Sorry about your brother, Bill.
对不起我的妈妈
I'm sorry for my ma.
我哥...
He was...
赶快把伞跳完吧
Let's get this over with.
比尔?
Bill?
我会在那里等你的
I'll meet up with you over there.
各位 罗医官开了晕机药给大家
Gentlemen, Doc Roe is handing these out for air sickness.
规定每人现在吃一颗 升空30分钟后再吃一颗
Orders are, "Every man takes one now, another, 30 minutes in the air."
中尉
Lieutenant.
第二排注意
2nd Platoon, listen up.
祝好运
Good luck.
上帝保佑你们
God bless you.
我们在集结区再见
I'll see you in the assembly area.
如果这很敏感的话 我想我们应该...
If the wire contacts are sensitive, then I think all we should have to do...
可恶 李
Goddamn, Lieb.
晕机药害我晕头转向
That airsick pill is making me loopy.
同盟国远征的陆海空军兄弟们
我们即将展开长征 为此我们已磨练很久
世界的目光都在你们身上
祝好运 让我们都向万能的神
为伟大而神圣的行动祈求祝福
盟军最高指挥官德怀特・艾森豪威尔将军